partnerfinds.com 2016-04-12

# Job Search Engine | PartnerFinds.com

## Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to PartnerFinds.com, and its associated websites and services. The intended use of this Privacy Policy is to inform users of our collection, use and disclosure practices regarding personal information that we collect through the Sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to data collected on any website or service under PartnerFinds’s control (collectively, the "Sites"), and does not apply to any other information or website.  
We reserve the right to update and change this Privacy Policy on occasion without notice. Continued use of the Sites after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.  
**Use of Collected Information**  
To perform a standard job search on the Sites, we do not require the transfer of any personal information. In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit (“Log Files”). If a user subscribes to the delivery of email-based jobs (“Email Job Alerts”), we collect that user’s email address, search phrase, and location (“Information”), and store the Information on our servers. This information is used to deliver, via email, relevant job openings to a subscriber. There is no charge to subscribe to Email Job Alerts. The information collected is not sold, leased, gifted, or shared with any third party service. A visitor may unsubscribe from Email Job Alerts by following the instructions which are included in the job alert email.  
In addition to standard user information (name, company, website, address, city, and zip), companies or agencies purchasing products and services, will be required to provide all information necessary to process billing transactions.  
To simplify the sign-in process and enhance the experience of the Sites, we offer the ability to sign in using certain 3rd party services (including, but not limited to: Facebook, LinkedIn, Google, & Yahoo). Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and PartnerFinds.com shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.  
**Security**  
You are responsible for ensuring that your log-in credentials (your username and password) are kept confidential. We have implemented technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure.  
**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" in a limited fashion to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends. A cookie is a text file that is either stored in your computer’s memory temporarily (a “session” cookie) or placed on your hard drive (a “persistent” cookie) by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  
You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website.  
**Questions & Feedback**  
Questions or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [support@PartnerFinds.com](mailto:support@PartnerFinds.com)
